They think, behind closed doors
and inside a condo, there's privacy.
What they don't know is no
sex video goes undiscovered!
I’m Shannon Sizon...
Welcome to another collection of videos
that should have stayed
in your phone's gallery.
Welcome to VMX TAPES VOLUME TWO!
For our first featured sex tape.
We thought it was a hidden camera.
Turns out, one of them
set the whole thing up!
That explains everything
Sissy here had no idea
their world of lust was
being caught on tape.
Damn, Jerome.
- Why?
- You're just gonna use me again, huh?
Come on. You enjoyed it, right?
I know you liked it.
It hurts.
Want me to do it again?
- Careful not to tear it!
- Relax.
Calm down!
Excited?
What am I, a parcel
you're gonna tear down?
Yeah.
I'll make you feel good.
It feels good.
Keep going.
Now, let's do the exciting part!
- It's good, right?
- Yeah.
Good, right?
- Hmm?
- So good.
You're so wet.
Because you're so hot!
Oh, shit!
Let's keep going.
- Can you?
- Yeah.
- You want more?
- Obviously.
Want to be on top?
Sure.
There.
Better.
You're getting good at this, huh?
Slow down.
I don't want to cum yet.
It's so good.
More!
My turn.
I'm about to cum!
Together, okay?
- Wait! Not inside!
- Don't worry.
It really feels way better inside.
I couldn't hold back.
You're an idiot, you know that?
You're so careless!
I couldn't help it.
- You felt too damn good.
- Geez...
I swear, if I get pregnant...
The next sex clip we're leaking...
They look like a couple.
The guy was making all these promises
that it would stay strictly between them.
Well... if we're watching it right now,
looks like someone broke that promise.
What a mess... and now it's out!
Babe, what are you doing?
- This is just for us.
- Why are you recording?
Really now?
If this leaks...
- I swear, it won't. trust me.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Alright, I'm trusting you.
Come on.
Feels good?
Yes, babe.
Go faster.
Should I put it in?
Yeah.
So good, babe.
- Good?
- Mhm.
Faster, babe.
You okay with having a video, babe?
It's fine.
Just don't leak it.
It's just for us, babe.
Are you close, babe?
Almost.
You want me to finish now?
- Don't rush it.
- Okay, okay.
Are you cumming?
I'm cumming.
Yes!
Want more?
You feel so good, babe.
Should I stop the video, babe?
Yeah, turn it off.
Speaking of leaks...
These days, videos
spread faster than gossip.
And if your file lands
in the wrong hands...
Good luck with that.
I'll leave you hanging on
the VMX sex tapes for now.
Come on... Play a game with me.
They're going to give us
different scenarios—
Scenes that could happen to anyone...
We'll choose one of two answers:
DELETE OR LEAK!
If it's DELETE,
that means erase it immediately
before anyone sees.
But if it's LEAK,
let the video go viral!
Here's the twist for
every DELETE answer,
you have to take off
one piece of clothing,
while you're watching this.
Make sure no one is
watching you right there!
Lock the door.
Or if you're outside,
head to a bathroom stall.
Game?
Scenario one.
You're checked into a hotel.
While changing out of your bra,
you notice your laptop webcam
has been on the entire time.
You have no idea if
anything was recorded or not.
DELETE OR LEAK?
Hmm... If it were me,
I'll let it leak.
I'm sure I look gorgeous on that video.
Scenario two.
You're playing with yourself.
DELETE OR LEAK?
Delete!
Because I chose delete,
I'll bring this down.
Scenario three.
You and your partner did
69 in an office blind spot.
But you didn't realize there was
another CCTV camera catching everything!
DELETE OR LEAK?
If it were me... We'd leak it.
I'm sure we both look hot in it.
Scenario four.
You're giving your ex
a break-up blowjob,
but he's secretly recording you.
You saw the video on his
phone while he's asleep.
DELETE OR LEAK?
If it were me, delete!
He's already an ex.
He should be forgetten.
And because I chose delete...
I hope you guys are doing it too!
No cheating here!
Scenario five.
You see a video on
your boyfriend's laptop
when he came on your face.
DELETE OR LEAK?
Me, I say leak it!
That's one of our fantasies.
Damn! It was so hard to choose!
Looks like a lot of phones are gonna
need to be locked after this game, huh?
But DELETE OR LEAK is over.
And it's time to go back to the tapes
that no one else was supposed to see.
That game earlier was so fun, right?
Makes you really want to get a massage.
Speaking of home massages...
let's be real, stories about
"extra service" are everywhere.
In this next clip, it's his first
time seducing a masseuse.
So, it wasn't just muscle
tension that got released,
she also ended up draining out
all that fluid he'd been saving up!
But it's a whole different story
when what should've stayed inside
the four corners of that room leaks out.
You okay there?
Sir, you're here.
Give me a sec
- I'll just use the restroom.
- Go ahead. I'll wait here.
You good?
- Are you ready, sir?
- Yes. Let's start.
How old are you?
I'm eighteen, sir.
So have you been doing massages long?
Yes—
Oh, actually no.
Just a few months.
So you're pretty new to this.
Yeah, I'm still new.
Even though you're new, I'm assuming...
Aside from massages,
you offer a little extra on the side?
I do.
But my rate is high.
Come on.
Don't underestimate me like that.
It's not that.
But if you can afford,
then yeah, sure.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of you.
Let's finish up this massage,
so we can get to it.
Just make sure you take care of me, okay?
Don't worry.
I've got you covered.
Feels good?
Yes... You feel amazing.
You're good at this.
Tired already, sir?
Yeah.
Your payment sir, okay?
Don't worry.
I'll pay you.
Let's do this again next time, okay?
Now go ahead and get dressed.
Here it is—our next clip
is basically part two of
the last one we watched!
The masseuse came back for round two.
Their video is way more intense this time
because they tried out
quite a few positions.
Hello sir.
- Hello.
- Should I massage you?
No need.
You already know the drill.
Let's start.
Come closer.
- You okay?
- Yes, sir.
Stop calling me, sir.
This is our second time already.
Don't worry. I got you.
Sir.
You good?
Yes, sir. Just tired.
Really? You got tired?
Don't worry.
Like last time,
I got you.
Alright, sir.
Alright.
I'll get dressed.
A massage is like a relationship,
if you rush it, you won't enjoy it.
We're not done with the
masseuse story just yet.
Because in our next clip, the
masseuse gives her client a blowjob.
And as a reward, the
guy takes her doggystyle!
Wait a sec!
Come in.
Good afternoon, sir.
Good afternoon. Have a seat.
I'll go to the restroom first.
Alright, sir.
How are you?
I'm good. You, sir?
Good.
You live alone, sir?
Yep.
I'll lay here, okay?
Okay.
How old are you?
I'm eighteen.
Have you been doing
this job for a long time?
Yes, sir.
Was your commute far coming here?
Yes. I'm from Rizal, sir.
Besides the massage,
do you offer anything else?
Depends on what the customer wants.
So if there's something
else I want you to do,
would you agree to it?
Of course, sir.
Okay.
Don't worry,
I got you.
Just do whatever I want.
Just make sure you
take care of me, okay sir?
Of course. How could I not?
Just make sure it feels really good, okay?
What do you prefer, sir?
Hard or relaxed?
I prefer it hard.
It's up to you.
Make it feel extra good, alright?
Sure, sir.
Does this feel better, sir?
Keep going. Just keep doing that.
You okay?
Yes.
You, sir?
Sir!
Ouch!
You're so good.
Let's do it again next time.
Sure, sir.
In our next clip...
A girl gives away her virginity
to the guy in bed with her.
What was supposed to be a secret surrender
turned into a public viewing!
Ouch!
Wait. I think we should stop.
Don't worry.
You're not sure of
what you're doing.
I'll make you feel good.
Don't worry.
Calm down.
It feels like you're
taking advantage of me.
Be gentle!
You'll like this.
You already know what to do, right?
You know that’s how it is, right?
I'll make you wet.
Don't worry.
I’m scared.
Try this out first.
Just wait...
- Wait!
- Come on!
Wait.
It hurts!
You're getting way too excited there.
Don't worry, I'll make you feel good.
It's ticklish!
Should I put it in?
They said, that will hurt.
Nah. You'll like this.
Wait, wait. Be gentle.
I will.
Wait. Take it slow.
Wait, wait stop!
Be gentle!
Shit, it hurts!
Wait, wait stop!
It's good, right?
Right?
I feel sore.
It feels so good with a virgin.
It hurts, but it also feels good.
Told you.
You okay?
Good, right?
Do you love me?
You're so wild.
Want it doggystyle?
Dogstyle. Dogstyle.
Bend over!
I came inside you.
I knew it!
Sorry.
You asshole!
I couldn't help it.
It feels good.
It’s okay.
I won't do it again next time.
There's no next time!
I'll just get my towel.
What if I get pregnant?
You won't.
You moron.
Hold on! We're not done yet!
We've pulled out one last video
that you definitely need to see!
For our big finale... this is
supposedly the couple's final scandal.
Both of them knew they were
filming themselves having sex,
so they really put on a show!
Look here, babe.
What's that? Stop recording!
- Stop that.
- It's just between us.
What if your phone gets hacked later?
It won't.
Wanna try making a video next time?
You've got some nerve, huh?
Come on. Just a try.
I don't want to.
- Feels good.
- Stop that.
Relax.
I'll only show you.
Hold it.
Don't let this leak.
[muttering]
Huh? That's for my phone only.
Please eat me.
You smell good.
Give it to me.
I'll take a video of you.
Wait.
Hold the camera.
I'm gonna put it now.
It feels good, right?
You're liking it?
Tell me if you're about to cum.
Wait, the video.
Look at the video.
You enjoying?
Want to do it doggystyle?
Can you handle it?
It's cold!
I'm close.
Are you almost done?
Faster! Faster!
I'm cumming!
Don't you dare upload this!
Don't worry too much.
Trust me.
Those are just a few of the scenes
caught by the eyes that never sleep.
Once we find the tape... you
already know what happens.
If I were you, make
your passwords stronger,
or better yet, just delete it!
Until next time, when
another scene gets caught...
VMX Tapes Volume Two.